

## Producer / Project Manager

acjh13.github.io



acjh13@gmail.com



Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

# **Industry Experience**

Junior Producer | Lionfish Studios Pte Ltd - Various Projects Mar 2021 - Present

- Manage communications between development team and stakeholders
- Manage in-house and outsourced development
- Assist in overseeing project milestones and releases
- Coordinate project development with multiple cross-functional teams

**Production Intern** | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - Final Fantasy Brave Exvius Sept 2020 - Feb 2021

- Maintained event lists for content updates with Google Sheets and Confluence
- Responsible for Design team's Sprint Planning and follow up with Jira
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to streamline and automate various production workflows

## On-Campus Experience

Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore - Game Production Class Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

Advised ~10 student teams on project management and game production

# **Academic Projects**

### **Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer**

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted Agile methodology with weekly Scrum meetings and Kanban boards
- Created cross-department workflows for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

### **Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer**

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!

## Education

## Bachelor of Science in **Computer Science and Game Design**

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 - Apr 2021

- Dean's Honour List, Fall '19
- Exchange Student DigiPen Redmond, Summer '19

### Skills

#### Soft Skills

**Effective Communication Problem Solving Conflict Resolution Project Ownership Team Management** 

### **Management Methods**

Agile Scrum Kanban

#### **Management Software**

Jira / Trello Confluence Google / Microsoft Suite Slack / Discord HacknPlan

#### **Software & Tools**

Git / SVN Microsoft Office Visual Studio Unity Unreal Engine 4 Custom Game Engine(s)

## **Programming Languages**

C / C++ C# Python JavaScript

#### Spoken Languages

English (Native) Mandarin (Limited)